Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XVI: Video
  - [My Mother #27 Second Part], undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0126_a)
    TRT: 00:09:03
  - [Shirley Titles], undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0127_a)
    TRT: 00:07:53
    This tape primarily has no picture, only sound. Music and title cards for "My Mother Shirley."
  - [Shirley Israel War Edit], undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0128_a)
    TRT: 00:15:09
    The tape primarily features television coverage of the war in Israel. In the final five minutes, Rivers sings "My Yiddishe Mama".
  - Shirley 9, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0129_a)
    "Work Reel" for Rivers's work, "My Mother Shirley", containing footage around Rivers's mother's apartment and interview footage with Shirley and Diana Molinari.
  - Shirley Work Reel, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0130_a)
    TRT: 00:12:09
    "Work reel" for "My Mother Shirley".
  - Shirley 13, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0131_a)
    TRT: 00:34:12
  - Peter Beard's Backyard Front Titles, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0132_a)
    TRT: 00:21:45
    Tape begins with black and white footage of Rivers interviewing his mother from behind the camera. The main contents of the tape are the title cards for Rivers's work, "Peter Beard's backyard", which documents a visit to Peter Beard's home in Africa.
    Peter Beard's Backyard
  - Smell I, II, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0133_a)
    TRT: 00:33:09
    Rivers and Michel Auder shoot footage for a project called "Smell".
    Smell
  - Smell - Peter Beard's House Montauk, 6 Sep 1975 (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0134_a)
    TRT: 00:15:49
    Rivers gives a video tour of the exterior of Peter Beard's Montauk house, and, with Michel Auder, shoots footage for a project called "Smell".
  - Smell Final Edit, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0135_a)
    TRT: 00:12:21
    Edited version of "Smell", a short work containing vignettes variously centered around the sense of smell.
  - RESTRICTED - Steven's New Job I, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0136_a)
    TRT: 00:33:39
    This item has been restricted due to content, as stipulated by the Larry Rivers Foundation.
  - Steven's New Job II, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0137_a)
    Title cards and opening scenes of "Steven's New Job". Rivers's son, Steven, discusses woprking as a sperm donor.
  - RESTRICTED - Edited Steven's New Job, undated (Box 118, Media ID: 293.0138_a)
    TRT: 00:33:06
    Steven's New Job
    This item has been restricted, due to content stipulated by the Larry Rivers Foundation.
  - Colorized Big B, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0139_a)
    TRT: 00:11:21
    Colorized edits of "Big B".
    Big B
  - Big B Edited from 1 inch, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0140_a)
    TRT: 00:10:22
    A television commercial parody starring Rivers as a salesman marketing a breast enhancement cream. Clarice Rivers portrays the satisfied customer.
  - Delbert & Glen I, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0141_a)
    Rivers joins musicians Delbert and Glen on tour in California.
  - Delbert & Glen, Group Playing, Listening to Radio, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0142_a)
    TRT: 00:323:11
    Delbert & Glen II
  - Delbert & Glen on the Way to San Diego, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0143_a)
    Alternate Title: Delbert & Glen III
  - Delbert & Glen, San Diego Auditorium, L.A. Soundcheck, L.A. Backstage, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0144_a)
    Delbert & Glen IV
  - Delbert & Glen, Backstage L.A., undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0145_a)
    TRT: 00:31:10
    Delbert & Glen V
  - Delbert & Glen - Big Al's Go-Go, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0146_a)
    TRT: 00:30:36
    Delbert & Glen VI
  - Delbert & Glen, Big Al's, Last Tape, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0147_a)
    TRT: 00:15:51
  - "A Quicky" (Advantages and Irresponsibility), undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0148_a)
    TRT: 00:25:13
    A series of vignettes (including "Big B") starring Rivers, Diana Molinari, and Clarice Rivers, and Niki de Saint-Phalle.
  - Ending for "Quicky", undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0149_a)
    TRT: 00:07:28
    No picture; voices can be heard over the tape for approximately the first two minutes.
    Ending Quicky
  - RESTRICTED - La Donne Mobile Final Version, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0150_a)
    TRT: 00:26:37
    La Donne Mobile
  - Peter B. Allen La Donne Mobile, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0151_a)
    TRT: 00:19:07
    Content Description
    Larry Rivers interviews Peter B. Allen on a couch at an aparment. Peter and two other men pass a phone back and forth. The video cuts to other people sitting on the same couch, Rivers asking them questions.
  - La Don Nay Mub EE Lay (Women Is Fickle), undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.152_a)
    BW/Sound
    TRT: 00:33:42
    A satirical advertisement for Big B breast enlarging cream. Larry Rivers talks about masturbating on a chair in his parents house. A women giving birth via a cesarean section in a hospital operating room. A woman and a man feeding a crying toddler boy in a high chair and talking about rasing him. Opera scene at end.
  - Twig I, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0153_a)
    TRT: 00:28:57
    A script reading performed in a living room. Shot clip of a motorcylce rally outside. Inside an artists studio. Inside of an airplane during take-off. At a California farm stand. A hurdy-gurdy man with a monkey on a leash. Street scenes.
    Alternate Title
    Twig
  - Twig II, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0154_a)
    TRT: 00:30:33
    People planning a movie shoot and holding auditions.
  - Twig III - Algonquin, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0155_a)
    TRT: 00:32:35
    People planning a movie in an apartment. People arguing over script and casting. Someone shooting heroin. New York CIty street scenes. Interview of a cop on the street. Interview with a guy selling belts on the street. Guy selling belts has a confrontation with the cops. Some people on the street talk to the camera about shoppping for clothes.
    DVD access copy available by appointment.DVD access copy available by appointment.
  - Twig 14th Street, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0156_a)
    TRT: 00:23:11
    People rehearsing a script in an apartment. (Bad audio buzzing)
  - Edited Twig I & II, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0157_a)
    TRT: 00:32:23
    Edited version of people rehearsing a script in an apartment.
  - Doing the Village Idiot, undated [date last run 12/28/82] (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0158_a)
    TRT: 00:33:24
    Crime Special - Larry Rivers talking about murder while playing different personalites. Two women talking about comitting the perfect crime - one is in the bathtub the other coming her hair in front of the mirror. The woman in the bathtub stays the same but the other woman keeps changing. Bumper cars at an amusement park. A group of guys beat up another guy in a park. The two women planning the perfect crime - murder - pick up the village idot in their car. They take him home and kill him.
  - Edited Splits, Crime Special for Village Idiot, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0159_a)
    TRT: 00:29:02
    Switching through television stations. Lots of dead space in this tape. Crime Special - Larry Rivers talking about murder while playing different personalites. Larry Rivers dancing to Mellow Yellow with a wig on cutting between Larry Rivers and another man talking about dancing and acting and Rimbaud and drugs. Larry Rivers dances in his underwear and exposes himself. Larry Rivers smokes a joint. Larry Rivers talks to the camera some more, rambling, about drugs, etc.
    Village Idiot
  - Village Idiot - Crime Special + First Take of Southampton Village Scene, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0160_a)
    TRT: 00:28:14
    Switching through television stations, mostly live musical performances and commercials. Crime Special - Larry Rivers talking about murder while playing different personalites.
    Man walking in park gets attacked by another group of men.
  - Chris - 2nd Take in S.H. Village for Village Idiot & Clips from the Birds, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0161_a)
    TRT: 00:25:39
    Man walking in park attacked by a group of men.
    A roughly 20min exceprt from Alfred Hitchcock's The Birds recroded from the television.
    Chris Village Idiot
  - Village Idiot - Bath Scene, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0162_a)
    TRT: 00:31:18
    A woman in a taking a bath reading "Les Chants de Maldoror" by Lautreamont (1846-1870) to another woman. There is a black cat in the scene. The women kiss.
    This scene is repeated several times; one of them contains brief oral sex.
  - Village Idiot - French Reel I, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0163_a)
    TRT: 00:33:54
    Scenes around an apartment as someone plays guitar and sings. Woman in bath reading; woman putting on makeup in front of mirror. Woman reads from "Les Chants de Maldoror" by Lautreamont (1846-1870) to the woman putting on makeup. They talk about committing murder. The women kiss. They get dressed, get in a car and drive around.
  - Village Idiot - French Reel II, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0164_a)
    TRT: 00:29:41
    Man in a cape walking by some water and picking flowers; feeds some geese. Two women driving in a car pick up this man - the village idiot. They take him home and listen to the Rolling Stones. They put some poison in a drink they are planning to give him. He makes-out with one of the women and th other one kills him with a blow to the head - no audio.
    Outside scenes on the street. The idiot is alive again.
  - Splits - Original, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0165_a)
    TRT: 00:31:02
    Larry Rivers dancing, sometimes in his underwear, sometimes naked.
  - Tattoo Titles, 1974 (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0166_a)
    TRT: 00:29:21
    Title card for "Tattoo: Spider Webb". After seven minutes, tape reverts to preexisting content. Rivers discusses an unfinished project he worked on with Diana Molinari. Footage of a performance by the Shinnecock tribe.
  - Diana's Tattoo 1, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0167_a)
    Diana Molinari gets a tattoo. Rivers films the process and interviews the artist, Spider Webb.
  - Diana's Tattoo 2, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0168_a)
    TRT: 00:17:25
  - Tattoo Party 1, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0169_a)
    TRT: 00:30:24
    Interviews with people with tattoos, at an event in a tattoo parlor featuring artist Spider Webb. Some interviews conducted by Steven Rivers.
  - Tattoo Party 2, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0170_a)
    TRT: 00:13:06
    Interviews with people with tattoos, at an event in a tattoo parlor featuring artist Spider Webb. Interviews by Steven Rivers.
  - American Couples I, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0171_a)
    TRT: 00:33:02
    Rivers visits a couple and their child in their home, and interviews them about their family life.
    American Couples
  - American Couples II Baby, Etc. Edited, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0172_a)
    Katy (featured in "American Couples I") leaves her son with a babysitter and discusses seeking a doctor's help to kick her heroin habit.
    American Couples II
  - American Couples Joe & Allen, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0173_a)
    TRT: 00:32:56
    Rivers visits Joe LeSueur and his partner at their home.
    Joe & Allen
  - American Couples Ciccone II, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0174_a)
    TRT: 00:32:34
    Rivers visits Antonio Ciccone, his wife and their adopted children. Rivers visits Ciccone's art studio and interviews him about his family life.
    Ciccone II
  - [Tianna/American Couple/Ciccone], undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0175_a)
    TRT: 00:10:53
    Rivers interviews a teenage girl at his house, then gives her the camera and instructs her on how to use it as she films him.
  - [Edited Couples I, Katy Close-Up], undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0176_a)
    TRT: 00:30:35
    Rivers interviews Katy (also featured in "American Couples I" and "American Couples II"). Near 6 minutes, the tape reverts to the same footage as "American Couples I".
  - [American Couples Katy II], undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0177_a)
    Rivers visits Katy while she's working at her parents' tobacco shop. (New footage begins at approximately 17 minutes.)
    Katy - American Couple II
  - Ciccone, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0178_a)
    Rivers visits Antonio Ciccone, his wife and their adopted children. He interviews them about their experience adopting children.
  - Amelio I American Couples, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0179_a)
    Rivers visits Amelio and Charles. Amelio, who lost one of his legs while serving in the armed forces, shows Rivers his wound.
    Amelio I
  - Amelio II, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0180_a)
    Original Format: 1/2 in. Open Reel.
    Rivers converses with Amelio and Charles.
  - The Artist Edited Version, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0181_a)
    TRT: 00:28:58
    Conceptual video footage made for the performance of "The Artist", an operatic adaptation of a Kenneth Koch poem by Koch, Rivers and Paul Reif.
    The Artist
  - [The Artist Dedication Landing Cherrywood Stairs Etc.], undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0182_a)
    TRT: 00:19:48
    Source footage for "The Artist".
  - The Artist Pacific Ocean, undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0183_a)
    TRT: 00:07:48
  - [The Artist 6], undated (Box 119, Media ID: 293.0184_a)
    TRT: 00:21:13
  - The Artist IV, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0185_a)
    TRT: 00:22:35
  - The Artist I, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0186_a)
    TRT: 00:31:26
  - [The Artist 8], undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0187_a)
  - [The Artist Cherrywood Steel Cigs Etc.], undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0188_a)
    TRT: 00:11:18
  - K. Koch the Artist I, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0189_a)
    Kenneth Koch and Rivers in a planning discussion of their collaborative opera, "The Artist".
  - K. Koch the Artist II, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 293.0190_a)
    00:06:57
  - Strange Tests, 17 Jan 1991 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0191_a)
    Color/Silent
    TRT: 00:12:40
    Inside an artists studio. Close-up shots of drawings. NYC sunset through windows.
  - Dorothy Miller, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0192_a)
    TRT: 00:18:35
    Rivers visits Dorothy Miller in her apartment as part of his WPA project, discussing her career, the WPA period and "Art for the Millions."
  - Shirley 16, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0193_a)
    TRT: 00:25:50
    Footage of Rivers's mother, for "My Mother Shirley". Rivers discusses growign old with his mother, and goes shopping for clothes with her.
  - Sonya I, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0194_a)
    TRT: 00:32:01
    At a dinner party, Rivers discusses folk and gypsy music with Sonya, a singer.
  - Sonya II, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0195_a)
    TRT: 00:22:45
    Sonya sings to piano accompaniment, and the discussion resumes around the dinner table. Final two minutes contain footage of a political demonstration in the street, shot from an apartment window.
  - 3 Octogenarians, 4 Aug 1975 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0196_a)
    Rivers interviews his mother and two of her friends on their lives and the aging process.
  - Mama's Baking Lesson, 03 - 04 Aug 1975 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0197_a)
    TRT: 00:32:10
    Rivers's mother instructs a group of women, including Rivers's wife and children, on making rugelach in the kitchen of Rivers's Southampton home.
  - Hampton Vaudeville 1, 1972 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0198_a)
    TRT: 00:15:26
    A stage performance fundraiser for the George McGovern presidential campaign.
    Hampton Vaudeville
  - Hampton Vaudeville 2, 1972 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0199_a)
  - Hampton Vaudeville 3, 1972 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0200_a)
  - Hampton Vaudeville 3, 1972 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0201_a)
    TRT: 00:25:40
  - Hampton Vaudeville 4, 1972 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0202_a)
    TRT: 00:27:06
  - Mural for McGovern, 1972 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0203_a)
    Contains footage of the Hamptons artists vs. writers softball game, where artists gathered to create a collaborative mural as a fundraiser for the George McGovern presidential campaign. Rivers interviews some of the participants and attendees about the McGovern campaign, often asking for opinions on rumors that he is gay.
  - [Not McGovern Explanation], undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0204_a)
    B&W/Silent
    TRT: 00:10:25
    Work reel footage. Experimenting with brightness and focus.
  - Nature Video, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0205_a)
    TRT: 00:30:45
    Larry Rivers and some people drive through the woods and then to a gravel pit. Shots of heavy machinery. Then they go to the beach (College Point?). Then they go somwhere where some guys are slaughering chickens in their backyard - could also be a small-scale chicken farm. Hiking through the woods to an abandoned gazebo. Someone pulls a birds nest out of a bush. More walking through the woods.
  - [Panel, Bridgehampton, Zoo], undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0206_a)
    TRT: 00:32:27
    Robert Twig, Taylor Meade, Sylvia Miles, Rudolph and Charles Rydell discuss a film by Rivers called "Four and a Half", in which they all performed.
  - Aage (Oh-Uh) Accident, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0207_a)
    TRT: 00:31:55
    Larry Rivers and his friends have a discussion about a car accident one of them recently had.
    AAGE
  - Shark I, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0208_a)
    TRT: 00:24:07
    Larry Rivers and some people on a fishing boat. They go for a ride, possibly to fish; possibly to fish for sharks. They chum the water for sharks. A man explains and displays various fishing lures to the camera. This is exactly like if Larry Rivers made Jaws, but there was no shark or kids, just guys with mustaches on a boat talking about catching a shark.
    Shark
  - Shark II, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0209_a)
    TRT: 00:32:13
    Larry Rivers and his friends fishing for sharks. One of the guys fires a rifle into the water a few times. No sharks appear to be caught.
  - Shark III, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0210_a)
    TRT: 00:22:59
    Larry Rivers and his friends fishing for sharks. One of the guys fires a rifle at some seagulls. No sharks appear to be caught. They ride back to shore.
  - Accident on Little Plains Road July 10, 1976, T.V. Interviews Jean O'Leary, Bruce Voeller, 10 Jul 1976 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0211_a)
    Larry Rivers at the scene of the accident, which appear to be between two cars. This takes place on a leafy, suburban looking street. Larry interviews one of the people in the accident while she sits in an ambulance. She appears unhurt. Larry asks several different people who saw the accident to describe what happened. The last 10 minutes of the tape is a public access TV broadcast of a panel discsussion about gay rights.
    Accident on Little Plains
  - Hitchers, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0212_a)
    TRT: 00:30:17
    Larry Rivers and some people in a car. It looks like autumn. They discuss going to the beach. Shots of outside the car window. They go to the beach. Two of the guys start playing catch with a football on the beach, then they start swimming. The sea is pretty rough. They go to Larry's house. They talk about drugs and sexual fantasies.
  - 3 Girls; Mel Climbing, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0213)
    Format: 1/2 in. Open Reel
    3 Girls
  - Gino Piano, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0214_a)
    TRT: 00:26:01
    Someone (Gino?) playing the piano. A naked woman writhing on a bed. A woman dancing in an apartment. Larry is playing with exposure a lot in this reel. Close-up of lots of record covers. Some little girls playing with scraps of paper on the floor. An TV internview in Spanish. A TV clip from Maude. Clips from some other TV shows.
  - Last Mango, Village Idiot Partially Edited, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0215_a)
    TRT: 00:34:21
    Larry Rivers and a guy dressed up (maybe like Santa Claus?) talk about stuff. They wrestle each other then pretend they are having sex. Bathtub scene from Village Idiot.
    Last Mango
  - K. Koch, T. Southern - Special - Typing, 56 Caddy, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0216_a)
    TRT: 00:30:37
    Contains still image and action shots for use in Rivers's collaboration with Kenneth Koch on a performance adaptation of Koch's poem, The Artist. Koch and Rivers adapted the poem, with Paul Reif, as an opera to be performed at the Whitney Museum. Final ten minutes features a conversation with Kenneth Koch, Diana Molinari, Terry Southern, and Rivers.
    Koch
  - DEACCESSIONED - Zoo, Bridgehampton, undated (Media ID: 293.0217)
    TRT: 00:32:06
  - Brigid's Fish Dinner, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0218_a)
    A dinner party hosted by Brigid Berlin.
  - Christmas '74 Pageant, Charles & Mary, "Carmen", 1974 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0219_a)
    TRT: 00:19:58
    Christmas '74
  - One Hundred Miles to New York I, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0220_a)
    TRT: 00:31:05
    Rivers tapes the trip from the Hamptons to New York City. He operates his camera from the backseat of a car driven by Michel Auder. Rivers aims his lens at landmarks and other drivers on the highway, narrating the trip.
    100 Miles to N.Y. I
  - One Hundred Miles to New York II, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0221_a)
    TRT: 00:32:20
    Rivers and Michel Auder drive back to the Hamptons from New York City, stopping off at a cemetery before leaving the city.
    100 Miles to N.Y. II
  - Bob Collacello's Parents, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0222_a)
    TRT: 00:22:08
    Larry Rivers interviews Bob Collacello's parents in their backyard. They live in Long Island now but they talk about why they liked living in New York City. They talk politics.
  - David & Judy, Party's End, undated (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0223_a)
    TRT: 00:19:54
    A garden party.
    David & Judy
  - July 4, 1973 I, 4 Jul 1973 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0224_a)
    TRT: 00:22:55
    4th of July parade in the Hamptons.
  - [July 4th, 1973 Tape 1], 4 Jul 1973 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0225_a)
    TRT: 00:23:06
    July 4th, 1973
  - [July 4th, 1973 Tape 2], 4 Jul 1973 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0226_a)
    TRT: 00:09:51
    July 4th, 1973 2
  - July 4th, 1975 I, 4 Jul 1975 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0227_a)
    TRT: 00:32:44
    Rivers visits the Southampton Fourth of July Parade. Before the parade, Rivers visits with firemen from a local department who built a float for the parade. At the parade, Rivers interviews attendants and participants.
  - July 4th, 1975 II, 4 Jul 1975 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0228_a)
    TRT: 00:21:24
    Rivers visits the Southampton Fourth of July Parade and interviews some of the participants and audience members.
  - July 5th Parade, 1976 I, 5 Jul 1976 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0229_a)
    Rivers visits the Southampton Fourth of July Parade and interviews participants and audience members.
  - July 5th Parade, 1976 II, 5 Jul 1976 (Box 120, Media ID: 293.0230_a)
  - Brigid's Cake Mix, undated (Box 121, Media ID: 293.0231_a)
    TRT: 00:33:51
    Brigid Berlin lies on Rivers's bed, eats and spreads chocolate cake over her nude body, and talks on the telephone with, among others, Andy Warhol.
  - Jerome's Farewell, Pool, undated (Box 121, Media ID: 293.0232_a)
    TRT: 00:28:30
    Tape begins with cuts between silent footage of Charles Rydell seeing off a departing Jerome and footage of Rydell discussing the scene. Followed by footage of swimmers in Rydell's pool and Rydell in discussion with Rivers about art and artists.
    Jerome's Farewell
  - DEACCESSIONED - Poolside '78, 1978 (Media ID: 293.0233)
  - Public Beach at Southampton, 24 Jul 1975 (Box 121, Media ID: 293.0234_a)
    TRT: 00:31:16
    Beach scenes. Larry interviews some people about crime in New York City and current events. Larry interviews some 15 year old girls. A boy gets burried in the sand.
    Public Beach
  - Songs, Songs, Songs, undated (Box 121, Media ID: 293.0235_a)
    TRT: 00:15:58